I have never sold so much paçoca
in my life using this idea.
the paçoca
one vote.
put it here that lula is winning
because the pocket people
starts voting to beat the squid
and the guy who is squid will vote to win the pocket.
vote for the candidate you want,
but remember if the owner of the ballot box always wins
then it's just you to put here a paçoquinha of a photo
can see
if you want to put on your candidate
I change the score here
a paçoca,
a real one,
who do you prefer?
all good,
a paçoquinha and a glass
bora? hand
none,
this is your nail owner,
Is it on?
I win the old three,
can catch.
oops,
good beauty,
just take a little bro,
then
feel free.
Valeu. bye,
goodbye.
and there brother,
go who?
pocket squid or none?
who will vote here
pick it up,
send it to see bro
will check everything.
We're with your brother,
okay.
tamo together.
thank you brother,
it's us guy it's not shit,
the guy even stopped to vote in the pocket.
bro,
one vote,
a real one,
five votes
can look smooth
bro then the crowd asks,
Who's filming?
I arrive in the city time guys
Bro I speak brother,
there's how you can hold it there.
Valeu cauê right bro?
tamo together hand
there's a paçoquinha for you
It is really?
thank you brother,
,
strengthened
dear uncle,
wants a paçoquinha
can catch bro,
can catch,
can catch.
we are at.
rush
and then the time is us.
thanks, thanks.
stay with god saw?
tamo together,
is already preparing that it was an explosion.
it's on.
eighty-nine and thirty more here ó,
two hundred eighty-four on the count and there
caraca mano,
It's time here.
satisfaction.
tomorrow there is more video.
eight and a half in the morning.
tamo with hand.